Guide to the Kurt Wolff Archive
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Box and Folder List
  - Reisiger, Hans, 1922 (Box 6, Folder 246)
  - Rilke, Rainer Maria, 1913-25 (Box 6, Folder 247-48)
  - Roland-Holst, Henriette, 1919-21 (Box 6, Folder 249)
  - Rolland, Romain, 1919-36 (Box 6, Folder 250-51)
  - Rouveyre, André, 1914-25 (Box 6, Folder 252-54)
  - Sauerlandt, Max, 1917-23 (Box 7, Folder 255)
  - Scheerbart, Paul
    - Correspondence [with transcripts], 1908-11 (Box 7, Folder 256-60)
    - Das Perpetuum mobile, [1908?], 1910 (Box 7, Folder 261-63)
  - Scheler, Max, 1916-17, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 264)
  - Schickele, René
    - Correspondence, 1913-35, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 265-71)
    - Papers, 1915-33, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 272)
  - Schmidtbonn, Wilhelm August
    - Correspondence, 1914-22 (Box 7, Folder 273-74)
    - Correspondence and papers, 1921-23, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 275)
  - Schmidt-Rottluff, Karl [with some transcripts], 1920 (Box 7, Folder 276)
  - Schmitz, Hermann Harry [with transcripts], 1911-13 (Box 7, Folder 277)
  - Schneiderfranken, Joseph (Box 7, Folder 278)
    See: Bô Yin Râ Box 1, folder 19a
  - Seewald, Richard [with transcripts], 1916-20 (Box 7, Folder 279)
  - Siemsen, Hans [with transcripts], 1920 (Box 7, Folder 280)
  - Simmel, Georg, 1916-17 (Box 7, Folder 281)
  - Spengler, Oswald [with transcript], 1917-23 (Box 7, Folder 282)
  - Stadler, Ernst [with transcripts], 1913-14 (Box 7, Folder 283-84)
  - Starke, Ottomar, 1915-20, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 285-86)
  - Sternheim, Carl, 1911-18 (Box 7, Folder 287-89)
  - Suarès, André, 1922 (Box 7, Folder 290)
  - Tagore, Rabindranath, 1914-22 (Box 7, Folder 290a)
  - Thoma, Hans, 1914 May 15 (Box 7, Folder 291)
  - Toller, Ernst [with transcripts], 1919-23 (Box 7, Folder 292-94)
  - Trakl, Georg [with transcripts], 1913-14 (Box 7, Folder 295-97)
  - Tzara, Tristan, 1919-21 (Box 7, Folder 298)
  - Unold, Max [with transcript], 1917 (Box 7, Folder 299)
  - Unruh, Fritz von
    - Correspondence, 1916-29, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 300-14)
    - Papers and third party correspondence, 1916-25, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 315)
  - Velde, Henry van de, 1918-19 (Box 8, Folder 316)
  - Vischer, Robert, 1919 (Box 8, Folder 317)
  - Voigt, Hans Henning, Baron von [Alastair, pseud.]
    - Correspondence, 1911-30, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 318-29)
    - Letters from Gabrielle Betz; papers, 1920-26, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 330)
    - Die Schuldlosen, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 331-34)
  - Walser, Robert: correspondence and poem: Handharfe am Tag, 1912-19, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 335)
  - Wassermann, Jakob, 1910-22 (Box 8, Folder 336)
  - Wedekind, Frank, 1912-22 (Box 8, Folder 337)
  - Weiss, Emil Rudolf [with transcripts], 1911-16 (Box 8, Folder 338)
  - Weiss, Ernst, 1920-22 (Box 8, Folder 339)
  - Wells, Catherine; Wells, H.G. (Herbert George), 1921-22 (Box 8, Folder 340-41)
  - Wells, H.G. (Herbert George): papers, 1922, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 342)
  - Werfel, Alma (Box 8, Folder 343-45)
    Empty folders
    See: Mahler, Alma Box 6, folders 210a-c
  - Werfel, Franz
    - Correspondence [with transcripts], 1912-20 (Box 9, Folder 346-82)
    - Correspondence [with transcripts], 1920-38 (Box 10, Folder 383-91)
    - Three poems from Beschwörungen: "Ballade von den Begleitern," "Angst," and "Schafe" (Box 10, Folder 392)
    - Poems from Gerichtstag, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 393-95)
    - Der jüngste Tag [with transcript], n.d. (Box 10, Folder 396)
    - Die Troerinnen des Euripides, 1914 (Box 10, Folder 397-98)
    - Wir Sind, [1914?] (Box 10, Folder 399-401)
    - "Das Opfer" from Wir Sind, [1914?] (Box 10, Folder 402-03)
    - Table of contents and afterword from Wir Sind, [1914?] (Box 10, Folder 404)
    - Three pencil sketches, [1913?], n.d. (Box 10, Folder 405)
    - Papers and printed poems, 1912-17, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 406-07)
    - Third party correspondence, 1914-16 (Box 10, Folder 408)
    - Third party correspondence; envelopes and miscellaneous, 1915-19, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 409)
  - Wilhelm, Richard [with transcript], 1928 Jun 12 (Box 10, Folder 410)
  - Wölfflin, Heinrich [with transcripts], 1920-21 (Box 10, Folder 411)
  - Wolfenstein, Alfred [with transcripts], 1917 (Box 10, Folder 412)
  - Wolfskehl, Karl and Renate, 1924-35 (Box 10, Folder 413)
  - Wyneken, Gustav [with transcripts], 1915-22 (Box 10, Folder 414)
  - Zech, Paul [with transcripts], 1911-23 (Box 10, Folder 415)
  - Zuckmayer, Carl, 1920-21 (Box 10, Folder 416)
  - Zur Mühlen, Hermynia von, 1919-23 (Box 10, Folder 417)
  - Zweig, Arnold, 1912-14 (Box 10, Folder 418)
  - Zweig, Stefan, 1911-30 (Box 10, Folder 419)
  - Adminstrative File, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 420)
  - Hansenclever, Walter Adminstrative File, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 421)